jenjobs.com 2014-11-23

# Job Vacancy | Job Search | Online Jobs in Malaysia | Jawatan Kosong : JenJOBS

**A. Personal Data Protection Act 2010 Notice**

This notice is issued pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (“Act”) (“Privacy Notice”). It explains the type of data we collect or have collected and how we collect the data, the purposes of processing such data, the parties we disclose or have disclosed the data to and the choices available to you including how to access and correct such personal data.

**B. Personal Data Protection Principles**

This Privacy Notice explains-:   
1\. Consent of data subject   
a. How we obtain personal information and your consent   
b. Acknowledgement & Consent   
c. How we process your personal information   
d. Type of personal information we collect   
2\. Contact details of our company   
3\. Third parties to whom the company may disclose your personal data to;   
4\. How Jenjobs.com safeguards the confidentiality and security of your personal information.   
5\. Retention standard   
6\. Data integrity standard   
7\. Data access request

**1\. CONSENT OF DATA SUBJECT**

**(a) COLLECTION OF PERSONAL DATA & YOUR CONSENT**

Personal information is obtained when you register for a JenJOBS.com account and also when you login to your account to fill in your profile details. When providing your personal information, you agree to our privacy policy and provide consent to JenJOBS.com and its holding company Agensi Pekerjaan Jen Software to process your personal data. If you do not register, we cannot provide you with our services. 

**(b) ACKNOWLEDGEMENT & CONSENT**

By registering an account with us, you acknowledge that you are of the age of 18 years or older and have read and understood the entire Privacy Policy and hereby give your consent to the processing or continued processing of your Personal Data in accordance herewith. If you are under the age of 18 please obtain consent from your parents, guardian or person who has parental responsibility over you. If you do not agree with the privacy policy please do not register and stop browsing our website www.jenjobs.com

**(c) NATURE OF BUSINESS AND PURPOSE OF COLLECTION OF DATA**

We are a recruitment agency operating an online job portal www.jenjobs.com

We are tasked with helping jobseekers find the right employers and vice versa. Therefore, the recruitment process requires a specific amount of information to be collected from both parties in order successfully match the right jobseeker to the right employer.

_Purpose 1_

We also collect personal data for the following reasons:-

  * using our online services www.jenjobs.com
  * verification and prevention of fraud
  * to notify jobseekers of available jobs which they may be interested in
  * to notify employers of candidates who have applied to their job vacancy
  * to allow employers to contact job applicants
  * to allow employers to conduct resume search and retrieve jobseekers resume
  * to conduct research and development so that we can improve our service
  * to provide customised content to users
  * to obtain statistics and analyse the usage of our website
  * to inform users of updates , newsletters, surveys, & promotion related to JenJOBS.com

_Purpose 2_

Furthermore, we may also collect personal data to inform our users of other goods and services offered by us, our partners, affiliates, and other third party vendors which may be of interest. You may choose to opt out from this option.

**(d) LIST OF PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED**

For the purposes of processing your job application, Jenjobs.com may collect the following personal data from you:-

  * Email
  * Full name
  * Gender
  * Telephone/Handphone number
  * Nationality
  * Date of birth
  * Academic qualification & certification
  * Job Preference and position
  * Photo of user
  * Address
  * Additional social information; website, twitter, linkedin, & facebook
  * Resume
  * I/C or Passport No.
  * Race
  * Citizenship
  * Marital Status
  * Language skills
  * Computer skills
  * Soft Skills
  * Working Experience
  * Credit/Debit card details
  * References
  * Logo of company
  * ROC No.
  * Company Name

**Use of Cookies**

Cookies are parcels of text sent by a server to a web browser and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time the User accesses that server. Cookies are used for authenticating, tracking, and maintaining specific information about the Users, such as site preferences. The Company may use Cookies to help personalize and maximize the User's online experience and time online.

**2\. CONTACT DETAILS**

If you have further questions regarding our privacy policy, kindly contact us:-

ATTN : Compliance Officer

Phone number : 03-74935989   
Fax number : 03-74935998   
Email : customerservice@jenjobs.com

Address :   
806, Block B, Pusat Dagangan Phileo Damansara II,  
No.15 Jalan 16/11, Petaling Jaya, 46350 Selangor

**3\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA**

The company may disclose your personal information but not limited to the following parties:-

  * Employees in the company from the IT, Marketing Customer Service and Accounts department who assist in answering queries posted by the users.
  * Employers and other recruitment agencies who use our services have access to the applicant's resume and also search for resumes in our database.
  * Partners, Affiliates & relevant third parties including but not limited to the following; online payment gateway, mapping service, analytical & statistical service, etc.
  * The company may disclose and transfer the user's information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of the company's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of the company's assets. In addition, in the event the company becomes the subject of a winding-up proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, the company or its trustee in winding-up may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court. The users will be notified of sale of all or a substantial portion of the company's business to a third party via email or through a prominent notice posted on the site.
  * We may also disclose personal data if it is legally required to the relevant legal authority.
  * The company may share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to the Site (for example, the number of visitors to the Site) with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Site and how those visitors use the Site. The company may also aggregate data regarding job qualifications, schooling, age, experience level or other information relevant to the job search or competition among jobseekers for any such job. Such data may be made available to employers or fellow jobseekers.

**4\. SECURITY POLICY**

  * We have taken the following steps to ensure best practice in order to safeguard your personal data:-
    * All user registration requires you to key in a unique password. All passwords are encrypted
    * All online payment via our third party payment gateway are SSL encrypted
    * We deploy software & hardware security such as anti-virus & firewall
    * We ensure a schedule back up of your data from time to time
  * We cannot guarantee the security of your personal data as no form of electronic transfer is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot responsible for any data loss, theft or misuse.

**5\. RETENTION STANDARD**

  * JenJOBS.com will retain your personal data for the period necessary to fulfil all businesses and legal purposes.
  * Please be aware that the User's Personal Information will be available to all employers and advertisers using the website. If the company you currently work for happens to be one of the employers that are using the website, they may see your User's Personal Information in the database. Note that the employers and advertiser using the website may retain a copy of your User's Personal Information for their records. In this instance, the Company cannot be held responsible for the retention, use or privacy of the User's Personal Information in connection with these employers and advertisers.
  * We also cannot be held responsible for the retention of personal information which you have disclosed to third parties such as partners, affiliates & etc.

**6\. DATA INTEGRITY STANDARD**

  * We will send you reminders from time to time to ensure your personal information accurate, complete, & is kept up-to-date.
  * However, it is your responsibility to ensure personal information entered is accurate, complete, not misleading, and kept up-to-date.
  * It is possible, that JenJOBS.com or third parties including but not limited to employers or advertisers may call upon your references to verify the personal information which you have provided. Please ensure you have obtained consent from your references to provide their contact details.

**7\. DATA ACCESS REQUEST**

  * Under the Act, you have the right of access to your Personal Data to edit, update or change your personal information at anytime subject to the verification of your identity. You may login to your account at anytime with your email and password to add, edit, correct, delete your personal information.
  * JenJOBS.com has the right to refuse to entertain any requests for withdrawal of consent if there is reasonable doubt surrounding the identity of the person making the request.
  * You may choose who can view your resume in our database via setting the resume access level in your personal account. This only applies when employers and advertisers use our resume search service. If you apply for job vacancy, the respective employer or advertiser will have access to your personal information.
  * You can opt in or opt out from receiving job alert notification from JenJOBS.com
  * You can opt in or opt out from receiving marketing material from JenJOBS.com or other third party affiliates, partners, & etc.

**C. TRANSFER ABROAD**

Presently, all personal data are stored locally in Malaysia. However, it is possible that we may transfer personal data directly or indirectly abroad into other countries in the future, including without limitation, of the following reasons:-

  * Web hosting is moved overseas
  * Relevant partners, affiliates, and third parties overseas
  * Foreign third party who acquires the company
  * Other foreign service providers of the company

**D. UPDATE OF PRIVACY POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME**

The Company may amend the privacy policy from time to time for legal or regulatory reasons, or to ensure the proper and smooth operation of the website. We advise you to visit our website to obtain the latest version of the company's privacy policy. In the event that the user does not agree to the amendments, the user shall not continue to access, browse, view or use the Site and/or the Services.
